https://www.futureplus.com/site-policy/

FuturePlus Systems Policy
This site is owned and operated by FuturePlus Systems Corporation. At FuturePlus Systems, we recognize that many visitors to our site are concerned about both the information they provide to us and how we treat that information. As a result, we’ve developed the Privacy Policy described below. We may update or change the Privacy Policy from time to time, so please check in occasionally. If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, you can contact us at:
FuturePlus Systems Corporation
15 Constitution Drive
Bedford, NH 03110-6042
Attention: Corporate Legal Department
603 471-2734 (8 a.m. – 5 p.m. Eastern Time, M-F)
Please feel free to email us anytime via the “Contact Us” links on this site. We’ll be happy to answer your questions or hear your concerns.
Our Policy
FuturePlus Systems Corporation respects the privacy of every individual who visits our site or responds to our interactive advertisements. We don’t collect personally- identifiable information from you, unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. We don’t require you to register or provide information to us in order to view our site. If you register in order to use various features of our site, we use the information you supply for the purpose of providing the products or services you’ve requested. If you agreed to follow-up contacts by us or asked us to be put on our mailing list when you registered, we may also contact you from time to time. You can always change your preference for follow-up contacts just by emailing us at any time. We don’t share any information you give us with anyone outside of FuturePlus Systems.
In the email section of our site, we ask for some personally identifiable information, such as your name, address and phone number. We don’t share the information with anyone outside of FuturePlus Systems Corporation. We don’t use your email address for any purpose other than sending you information you requested. Where appropriate, we will specifically instruct children not to submit such information on our websites or advertisements. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child may contact us at the email address or address listed in this Privacy Statement if they would like this information deleted from our records and we will use reasonable efforts to delete the child’s information from our databases. Our site sometimes includes notices of promotions we are conducting, and we may permit you to enter electronically in some cases. If that occurs, we will use the information you provide for the purpose of conducting the promotion (e.g., to contact you if you’re a winner). We don’t share the information you give us with anyone outside of FuturePlus Systems Corporation.
Cookies
We do not use cookies when you visit our site.
Use of Site Material
Please don’t hesitate to make a single copy of a document or part of a document published by us on this site for your personal use, but please ensure that our copyright notice is clearly displayed on your copy. Please do not download documents, parts of documents, logos and other materials from our site for your own commercial purposes without our prior written consent.
Forward-Looking Information
Certain information on our site and certain information prepared by us and available on this site about our business and operations constitutes “forward-looking information” at various places on our site and is subject to the qualifications set forth in more detail where the information is contained.
Disclaimer of Warranty
Although we work very hard to provide you with the most current and accurate information on our site, we can’t and don’t warrant that everything you see on this site is up-to-date, error-free or complete. While we may periodically add, modify or delete any of the information on this site, we don’t make any commitment or assume any obligation or duty to do so, and you should assume
that the information is current and up-to-date only as of the date it is posted to this site. Neither we nor any of our consultants for this site will be liable for any direct, incidental, consequential or punitive damages arising out of your access to or use of this site.
Everything on this site is provided to you “AS IS,” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANATABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NONINFRINGEMENT.
Some jurisdictions may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties so this statement may not apply to you. Except as indicated otherwise, all of the material on our site is made available in order to provide you with information about our company, properties, marketing and business operations. We make no representations that the materials contained on this site are accurate or appropriate for users in locations outside of the United States. Some software on this site may be subject to export controls imposed by the United States and may not be downloaded or otherwise exported to certain countries. By downloading any software, you are representing to us that you are doing so in compliance with all applicable state and federal laws.
Software User License
Notwithstanding the above, use of downloadable software made available on this site is governed by this license.
© Copyright 2012, FuturePlus Systems Corporation. All Rights Reserved in the U.S.A. and other countries
We use cookies on our website to give you the most relevant experience by remembering your preferences and repeat visits. By clicking “Accept”, you consent to the use of ALL the cookies.Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on this website.
Request More Information/Quote
or Call: (603) 472-5905
Your name *
Your e-mail *
Email subject *
Your message *
3 + 4 =
Send
Request the FS2700 DDR5 Sideband Bus Protocol Analyzer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request a Memory Channel Validation Audit!
CLOSE
Request an Embedded Memory Testing Audit!
CLOSE
Request a Memory Analysis for HPA Validation Testing Audit!
CLOSE
Request a DIMM/SODIMM/DDR4/DDR5 Validation Testing Audit!
CLOSE
Request the FS2807 DDR4 Performance Counters Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the DDR Detective Probing Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the Combined DDR4 MSO Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the Combined DDR3 MSO Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the LPDDR3 FS2801 DDR Detective Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the DDR3 Detective Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the LPDDR4 DDR Detective Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2800A DDR4 Detective Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the LPDDR5 DDR Detective Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2602 DDR5 SO-DIMM Interposer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2601 DDR5 UDIMM Interposer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2600 DDR5 RDIMM/LRDIMM Interposer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2521 DDR4 SO-DIMM Interposer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2510AB DDR4 DIMM Interposer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2520 DDR4 DIMM Interposer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2352B DDR3 DIMM 2133 Interposer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2354 and FS2355 DDR3 SO-DIMM Interposers Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS2361 DDR3 DIMM 2400 Interposer Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS4520 CheckDPspec™ Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS4507 Remote SW Interface Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS4500 Probing Datasheet!
CLOSE
Request the FS4500 Series Datasheet!
×
